

# **ABOUT ME**

I have worked as a programmer in the such fields as financial and banking, media, sales, real estate-management, events organization and others.

I'm passionate about mobile development and cycling as a most lovely hobby. I'm always interested in new projects and glad to meet new challenges.

# **SKILLS**

Kotlin

Java

**Android SDK** 

CustomView

Rx.Java

Room

Dagger

Multimodularity

Cecerone

Clean Architecture, MVP, MVI

JavaScript

Cordova

# **LANGUAGE**

Russian (fluent)

English (intermediate)

# ARMAN BISEMBAEV

# Android Software Engineer

☐ arm.bisembaev@gmail.com

+7 (702) 184-89-57

Kazakhstan, Aktobe

■ www.linkedin.com/in/armanbis

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## ANDROID DEVELOPER

Feb 2022 - Currently

## Home Credit Bank, Moscow

My general duty here is working on a Home Credit Bank android application. Being a part of a team that have to keep the project in a correct technical state. Developing the core features, libraries and application interfaces which used by other mobile dev teams. Setting up and supporting CI/CD pipelines.

## ANDROID DEVELOPER

Feb 2020 - Feb 2022

#### MoeDelo, Moscow

Developing a big part of the functionality of the main entrepreneur app.

Participate in the development of product requirements.

Engage in the services of analytics, interacting with the marketing department. Increased the crash-free rate from 95% to 99%.

- Refactoring legacy
- Interaction with Backend teams (api development) and DevOps (assistance in setting up CI/CD)
- Interaction with the marketing team, engage in the services of analytics

## ANDROID DEVELOPER

Oct 2018 - Feb 2020

## NAI Becar, Saint Petersburg

During my work in the company, I have developed applications for real estate management. Contractor's application - to perform work on requests.

Application for the customer - for submitting applications.

Application for the head - to control performers.

- Development and support of native and hybrid mobile applications of the company
- Participation in planning the development process.
- Release management
- Interaction with the backend team

## ANDROID DEVELOPER + FULLSTACK

Jan 2016 - Oct 2018

## TBC Eurasia, Orsk

Developing a bulletin board app, a weather forecast app, a billboard

viewer app, a TV channel app, and a broadcast radio app.

I also developed most of the functionality of the company's web services, including api for applications.

MOBILE DEVELOPER 2014–2016

## Several side freelance projects

Made a several projects on Android Native and Ionic/Cordova.

It was something like getting the first commercial experience.

# **EDUCATION**

Specialist degree

Orenburg State University

Computer software and automated systems 2010 - 2015

# **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Moxy, Git, SQL, Angular2+, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, RxJs, NgRx, Ionic Framework, BigQuery, PHP